Guide to the Acquisitions Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Acquisitions Department, Yale University Library, records
1925-1985
RU 346
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
82.5
(172 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, card files, statistics, reports, and gift and acknowledgment files documenting gifts and materials received by the Acquisitions Department, Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-C (YRG 32-C), Records of Yale University Library departments and offices.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, card files, statistics, reports, and gift and acknowledgment files documenting gifts and materials received by the Acquisitions Department, Yale University Library.
Academic libraries -- Acquisitions; Libraries -- Gifts, legacies; Technical services (Libraries); Yale University. Library
- Records, circa 1932-1963; Accession 1972-A-015
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only
  - Gifts and Exchange Department
  - Harkness Gift File, 1947-1948 (Box 1)
  - Library Associates - Record of Gifts, 1952-1963 (Box 1)
  - Annual reports of the gift section to head of Order Dept, 1932-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1-19)
- Acknowledgments, 1972-1979; Accession 1985-A-063
  - Gift Correspondence, 1972-1979
    - A-G and gift continuation claims sent, 1972-1979 (Box 1)
    - H-S and S.C. discard reply letters, 1972-1979 (Box 2)
    - T-Z, 1972-1979 (Box 3)
- Memo on library collecting practices, 1976; Accession 1993-A-055
  - Memo on library collecting practices, 1976 (Box 1)
- Records, circa 1940-1958; Accession 1998-A-050 (Box 1–5)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Records, 1946-1979; Accession 19ND-A-113
  - Acknowledgements
    - 1946-1947
      - A, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - B, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - C - E, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - F - G, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - H - I, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - J - K, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - L - M, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - N - Q, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - R - S, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - V - W, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - X - Z, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1947-1948
      - A (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - B, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - C - D, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - E - F, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - G - H, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - I - K, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - L - M, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - N - Q, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - R - T, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - U - V, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - W - Z, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 1948-1949
      - A - B, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - C - D, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - E - F, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - G - H, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - L - M, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - N - 0, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - P - R, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - S - T, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - U - V, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - W - Z, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - 1949-1950
      - A, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - B, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - C, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - D - F, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - G - H, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - I - J, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - K - L, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - M - N, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - O - P, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Q - R, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - S - T, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - U - V, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - W, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - X - Z, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Yale, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - 1950-1951
      - A, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - B, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - C, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - D - F, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - G - H, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - J - L, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - M - O, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - P - R, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - S - T, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - U - V, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - W, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - X - Z, Yale, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - 1951-1952
      - A, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - B, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - C - D, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - E - F, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - G - H, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - I - K, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - L, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - M, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - N - P, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - Q - R, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - S - T, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - U - V, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - W - Z, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Yale, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - 1952-1953
      - A, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      - B, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      - C - D, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 76)
      - E - F, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - G - H, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - I - K, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 79)
      - L, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - M, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 81)
      - N, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 82)
      - O, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 83)
      - P - Q, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 84)
      - R - S, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 85)
      - T - V, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 86)
      - W - Z, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 87)
      - Yale, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 88)
      - Dealers - Library Associates, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - 1953-1954
      - A, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 90)
      - B, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 91)
      - C, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 92)
      - D - E, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 93)
      - F - G, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 94)
      - H, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 95)
      - I - K, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 96)
      - L - M, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 97)
      - N - O, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 98)
      - P - R, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 99)
      - S - T, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 100)
      - U - V, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 101)
      - W - Z, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 102)
      - Yale, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - 1954-1955
      - A, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 104)
      - B, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 105)
      - C, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 106)
      - D - F, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 107)
      - G - I, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 108)
      - J - K, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 109)
      - L, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 110)
      - M - N, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 111)
      - O - Q, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 112)
      - R, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 113)
      - S, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 114)
      - T - V, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 115)
      - W - Z, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 116)
      - Yale, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 117)
    - 1955-1956
      - A, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 118)
      - B, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 119)
      - C, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 120)
      - D - F, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 121)
      - G, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 122)
      - H - I, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 123)
      - J - L, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 124)
      - M - N, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 125)
      - O - Q, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 126)
      - R - S, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 127)
      - T - V, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 128)
      - W - Z, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 129)
      - Yale, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 130)
    - 1956-1957
      - A, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 131)
      - B, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 132)
      - C, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 133)
      - D - F, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 134)
      - G - H, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 135)
      - I - K, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 136)
      - L, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 137)
      - M - N, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 138)
      - O - Q, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 139)
      - R - S, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 140)
      - T - V, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 141)
      - W - Z, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 142)
      - Yale, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 143)
    - 1957-1958
      - A, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 144)
      - B, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 145)
      - C - D, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 146)
      - E - F, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 147)
      - G - H, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 148)
      - I - K, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 149)
      - L, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 150)
      - M - Mi, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 151)
      - Mo - N, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 152)
      - O - Q, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 153)
      - R, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 154)
      - S, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 155)
      - T - V, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 156)
      - W - Z, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 157)
      - Yale, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 158)
    - 1958-1959
      - A, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 159)
      - B - Be, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 160)
      - Bi - Bz, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 161)
      - C, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 162)
      - D, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 163)
      - E - F, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 164)
      - G, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 165)
      - H, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 166)
      - I - K, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 167)
      - L, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 168)
      - M, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 169)
      - N, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 170)
      - O - Q, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 171)
      - R, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 172)
      - S, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 173)
      - T - U, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 174)
      - V, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 175)
      - W, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 176)
      - X - Z, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 177)
      - Yale, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 178)
    - 1959-1960
      - A, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 179)
      - B - Bi, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 180)
      - Bl - Bz, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 181)
      - C, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 182)
      - D, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 183)
      - E - F, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 184)
      - G - He, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 185)
      - Hi - Hz, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 186)
      - I - K, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 187)
      - L, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 188)
      - Ma, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 189)
      - Me - Mz, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 190)
      - N, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 191)
      - O - Q, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 192)
      - R, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 193)
      - S, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 194)
      - T - V, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 195)
      - W - Z and list of acknowledgements sent in Mr. - Babb ' s absence, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 196)
      - Yale, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 197)
    - 1960-1961
    - A1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 198)
      - B - Be, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 199)
      - Bi - Bz, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 200)
      - C, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 201)
      - D, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 202)
      - E, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 203)
      - F, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 204)
      - G, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 205)
      - H - Ha, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 206)
      - He - Hz, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 207)
      - I - J, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 208)
      - K, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 209)
      - L, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 210)
      - Ma, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 211)
      - Me - Mz, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 212)
      - N, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 213)
      - O - Pi, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 214)
      - Po - Q, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 215)
      - R - Sc, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 216)
      - Se - So, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 217)
      - Sp - Sz, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 218)
      - T, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 219)
      - U - V, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 220)
      - W - Wh, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 221)
      - Wi - Z, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 222)
      - Yale, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 223)
    - 1961-1962
      - A, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 224)
      - B - Be, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 225)
      - Bi - Bz, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 226)
      - C - Co, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 227)
      - Cr - D, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 228)
      - E - F, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 229)
      - G, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 230)
      - H - Hi, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 231)
      - Ho - I, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 232)
      - J - K, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 233)
      - L - Le, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 234)
      - Li - Ma, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 235)
      - Me - Mz, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 236)
      - N, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 237)
      - O - Pa, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 238)
      - Pe - Q, 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 239)
      - R, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 240)
      - S - Se, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 241)
      - Sh - Sz, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 242)
      - T, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 243)
      - U - V, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 244)
      - W - Wh, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 245)
      - Wi - Z, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 246)
      - Yale, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 247)
    - 1962-1963
      - A, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 248)
      - B - Be, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 249)
      - Bi - Bz, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 250)
      - C - Cl, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 251)
      - Co - D, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 252)
      - E - F, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 253)
      - G, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 254)
      - H - Hi, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 255)
      - Ho - Hz, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 256)
      - I - J, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 257)
      - K, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 258)
      - L, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 259)
      - M - Ma, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 260)
      - Me - Mz, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 261)
      - N, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 262)
      - O - Pe, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 263)
      - Pf - Q, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 264)
      - R, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 265)
      - S - Sh, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 266)
      - Si - Sz, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 267)
      - T, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 268)
      - U - V, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 269)
      - W - Wh, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 270)
      - Wi - Z, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 271)
      - Yale, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 272)
    - 1963-1964
      - A, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 273)
      - B - Be, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 274)
      - Bi - Bz, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 275)
      - C - Con, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 276)
      - Coo - D, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 277)
      - E, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 278)
      - F, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 279)
      - G, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 280)
      - H - He, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 281)
      - Hi - Hz, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 282)
      - I - J, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 283)
      - K, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 284)
      - L - Le, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 285)
      - Li - Lz, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 286)
      - M, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 287)
      - N, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 288)
      - O, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 289)
      - P - Pe, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 290)
      - Pf - Q, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 291)
      - R, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 292)
      - S - Si, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 293)
      - Sl - Sz, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 294)
      - T, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 295)
      - U - V, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 296)
      - W - Wh, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 297)
      - Wi - Z, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 298)
      - Yale, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 299)
    - 1964-1965
      - A, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 300)
      - Ba, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 301)
      - Be, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 302)
      - Bi - Bz, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 303)
      - C - Sh, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 304)
      - Ci - Cz, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 305)
      - D, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 306)
      - E, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 307)
      - F, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 308)
      - G, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 309)
      - H - Hi, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 310)
      - Ho - Hz, 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 311)
      - I - J, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 312)
      - K, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 313)
      - L, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 314)
      - Ma, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 315)
      - Me - Mz, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 316)
      - N, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 317)
      - O - Pe, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 318)
      - Pf - Q, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 319)
      - R, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 320)
      - S - Se, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 321)
      - Sh - Sz, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 322)
      - T, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 323)
      - U - V, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 324)
      - W - Wh, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 325)
      - Wi - Z, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 326)
      - Yale, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 327)
    - 1965-1966
      - Ac - Aw, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 328)
      - Ba - Bd, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 329)
      - Bd - Bu, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 330)
      - Ca - Cu, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 331)
      - D, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 332)
      - E - F, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 333)
      - G, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 334)
      - Ha - He, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 335)
      - Hi - Hz, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 336)
      - I - J, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 337)
      - K, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 338)
      - L, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 339)
      - M, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 340)
      - N, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 341)
      - O, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 342)
      - P - Q, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 343)
      - R, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 344)
      - Sa - Sh, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 345)
      - Sh - St, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 346)
      - T - U, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 347)
      - V, 1965-1966 (Box 62, Folder 348)
      - W - Z, 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 349)
      - Yale, 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 350)
    - 1966-1967
      - A, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 351)
      - Ba - Bor, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 352)
      - Bos - By, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 353)
      - C, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 354)
      - D, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 355)
      - E - F, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 356)
      - G, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 357)
      - H, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 358)
      - I - K, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 359)
      - L, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 360)
      - M, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 361)
      - N, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 362)
      - O - Q, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 363)
      - R, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 364)
      - Sa - Sh, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 365)
      - Sh - Sz, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 366)
      - T - V, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 367)
      - Wa, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 368)
      - Wi - Z, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 369)
      - Yale, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 370)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1968 (Box 68, Folder 371)
    - 1967-1968
      - A, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 372)
      - Ba - Bt, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 373)
      - Bu - Bz, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 374)
      - Ca - Ci, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 375)
      - CI - Cz, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 376)
      - D, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 377)
      - E - F, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 378)
      - G, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 379)
      - H, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 380)
      - I - J, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 381)
      - K, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 382)
      - L, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 383)
      - Mc - Me, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 384)
      - Mi - Mz, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 385)
      - N, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 386)
      - O, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 387)
      - P - Q, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 388)
      - numbering error, no # 391, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 389)
      - R, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 390)
      - S, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 391)
      - T - V, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 392)
      - Wa - Wh, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 393)
      - Wi - Z, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 394)
      - Yale, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 395)
      - Library Associates, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 396 - 398)
      - American Nusical Theater Fund - J. H. Ottemiller, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 399)
      - American Musical Theater Fund - Robert L. Barlow, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 400)
      - James T. Babb Fund, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 401)
      - Robert J. H. Kiphuth, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 402)
      - Chancey Brewster Ticker, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 403)
    - 1968-1969
      - A, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 404)
      - B - Be, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 405)
      - Bi - Bz, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 406)
      - C, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 407)
      - D, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 408)
      - E - F, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 409)
      - G, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 410)
      - Hac - Har, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 411)
      - Has - Hz, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 412)
      - I - J, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 413)
      - K, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 414)
      - L, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 415)
      - M, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 416)
      - N, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 417)
      - O - Q, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 418)
      - R, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 419)
      - S, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 420)
      - T - V, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 421)
      - W - Z, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 422)
      - Yale, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 423)
    - 1969-1970
      - A, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 424)
      - B - Be, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 425)
      - Bi - Bz, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 426)
      - C, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 427)
      - D, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 428)
      - E, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 429)
      - F, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 430)
      - G, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 431)
      - Ha - Hh, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 432)
      - Hi - Hz, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 433)
      - I - K, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 434)
      - L, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 435)
      - M, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 436)
      - N, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 437)
      - O - Pa, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 438)
      - Pe - Q, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 439)
      - R, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 440)
      - S, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 441)
      - T, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 442)
      - U - V, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 443)
      - Wa - We, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 444)
      - Wh - Z, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 445)
      - Yale, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 446)
    - 1970-1971
      - A, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 447)
      - B - Be, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 448)
      - Bi - Bz, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 449)
      - Ca - Ch, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 450)
      - Ci - Cz, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 451)
      - D, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 452)
      - E, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 453)
      - F, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 454)
      - G, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 455)
      - Ha - Hi, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 456)
      - Ho - Hz, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 457)
      - I - J, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 458)
      - K, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 459)
      - L, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 460)
      - M, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 461)
      - N, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 462)
      - O - Pa, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 463)
      - Pe - Q, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 464)
      - R, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 465)
      - Sa - Sh, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 466)
      - Si - Sz, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 467)
      - T, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 468)
      - U - V, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 469)
      - Wa - Wi, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 470)
      - Wi - Z, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 471)
      - Yale, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 472)
      - Library Associates, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 473)
    - 1971-1972
      - A, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 474)
      - B - Be, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 475)
      - Bi - Bz, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 476)
      - C, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 477)
      - D, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 478)
      - E, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 479)
      - F, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 480)